https://clemson4wheel.com/privacy-policy

Search
Register
Log In
Your shopping cart is empty.
Register
Log In
Your shopping cart is empty.
Toggle navigation
Accessories
Air IntakesApparelATVsAutomotive LightingBeltsBrake SystemsCamshafts and ValvetrainCar CareCar ElectronicsCarburetionCargo ManagementChassis and SuspensionClutchesCoolingData LoggersDrivetrainElectricalEngine Dress-UpEngine PartsExhaustExteriorFastenersFiltersFuel InjectionFuel SystemsGasketsGaugesIgnitionInteriorJEEP Replacement PartsLiteratureOils and FluidsPerformance Chips and ProgrammersPlumbingPulleysSafetySensorsTiming PartsToolsTowing and AccessoriesTruck Bed and TailgateTurbochargers and SuperchargersWheels and TiresWinches and Accessories
Catalog
Top Categories
Truck and SUV Winches
Soft Tops and Accessories
Winch Mounts
Tonneau Covers - Hard Folding
Fifth Wheel Hitches and Goosenecks
Winch Accessories
Shop’s Open Til 5:30
Monday8:00 - 5:30Tuesday8:00 - 5:30Wednesday8:00 - 5:30Thursday8:00 - 5:30Friday8:00 - 5:30SaturdayClosedSundayClosed
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last updated: September 24th, 2019In short, we promise to do our dead-level best to protect the privacy of our visitors. We don't give away or sell your information to anyone, ever, and we keep our systems up to date with the latest security technology to prevent intruders from gaining access. We value you, our customer, and want you to return, and we know that if we compromise your information, you won't be shopping with us again. Thank you for choosing Clemson 4 Wheel Center, where you can shop with confidence.This Privacy Policy is intended to describe what types of information we gather about our users as well as how we use it. You'll also learn about what you can do to learn about or opt out of the data we collect (such information will be indicated in bold throughout this Privacy Policy). This Privacy Policy applies to the website located at www.clemson4wheel.com as well as any related websites or apps (mobile or desktop). Hereafter, this collection of related assets will be referred to as the "Site."Our digital infrastructure automatically captures no data pertaining to the domains or email addresses of our users except for data gathered through Google Analytics. We do collect the email addresses of users who communicate with us through email, but these are used only as they relate to our own internal evaluations. Cookies are used to the extent that they allow Clemson 4 Wheel Center customers to access their accounts.If you do not wish to receive future emails from us, notify us of your preference by emailing us at the address listed at the end of this Privacy Policy.We may collect information about you—such as your name and contact information—when you interact with our Site in certain ways (e.g., by making purchases or subscribing to email lists).This information may be shared with affiliates who are controlled by, who control, or who are under common control with Clemson 4 Wheel Center Inc. and Aftermarket Websites™.We may share this information, along with a record of any transactions you conduct on our Site or with us offline, with a third-party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver interest-specific advertising to you when you visit certain other websites. Data shared with third-party partners remain anonymous.Additionally, we may enlist the services of third parties to deliver services and marketing to you not limited to processing payments and orders or designing custom sites for your use. If personally identifiable information must be provided to any of these third parties, we will require that it be held to privacy standards that at least meet those outlined in this Privacy Policy.We employ cookies to allow our customers to log in to their accounts. We may create and implement additional cookies in order to provide you with online advertising tailored to your interests.We may direct you to third-party websites or suggest that you download a third-party application. Any such recommendation is presented for your convenience only; it does not signify our endorsement of the third party or its products or services. Clicking on such a link or downloading such an application will cause you to leave our Site. As part of this process, the third party may collect personally identifiable information from you. We do not oversee, nor can we be responsible for, these outside sources or their content. Be advised that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these extra-Site locations; we recommend that you take steps to understand how third parties will use your information before you agree to their terms of use.In the event that we buy or sell a company, or one or more of our affiliated companies merges with or is acquired by another company, we may transfer some or all of your information as a part of the transaction. We may do this to ensure that services currently being provided to you may continue, or for other business purposes.Our Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 13. We hereby ask that individuals under the age of 13 not provide personal information through our Site. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 without parental consent. Visit the Federal Trade Commission website to learn more about COPPA, or the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.We employ all reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of data collected about you at our Site.If you feel that this Site is not following its rules for data acquisition or use as stated in this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by mail, email, or telephone to resolve the matter. (Addresses and phone numbers appear at the bottom of this page.)This Privacy Policy may change at any time; alterations will be indicated by a revised “Last Updated” date at the top of this page. Changes become effective when they are posted to the Site. Your use of the Site following any change indicates your unconditional acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy, so we encourage all users to periodically visit this page in order to view the most current version of these user terms.In the event that you or those you represent do not agree to the use of your information as laid out in this Privacy Policy, you must cease your current use of this Site and not register for further use. If already registered, you must cancel your account and cease further use of this Site. Any continuation of use signifies your explicit agreement to be bound by and to comply with the terms laid out in this Privacy Policy; this agreement extends to any parties you might represent.Mailing AddressClemson 4 Wheel Center Incc/o Aftermarket Websites™ Privacy Manager10733 Clemson BlvdSeneca SC  29678Email Addresssales@clemson4wheel.comPhone Number864-882-0277
